{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51623404","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51623404","name":"Toney Island LLC","address":"13000 E. Warren ","zipcode":"48215","owner":"Antonio Henderson  ","licenseNumber":"253502","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-82.96669,42.39234","geojson":{"id":"51623404","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.966687667,42.39234138]},"properties":{"name":"Toney Island LLC","owner":"Antonio Henderson  ","address":"13000 E. Warren ","zipcode":"48215","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"253502","establishmentid":"51623404","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"2638","name":"Joy's Deli","address":"13131 Warren E.","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"5425","name":"Spud Headz","address":"12700 Warren E.","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"4472","name":"Eastside Soulfood","address":"12700 Warren E.","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"51623316","name":"Lonestar Catering","address":"12700 E. Warren","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"51623354","name":"Black Cloud Kitchen ","address":"12700 E. Warren ","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"208","name":"Colin Powell Academy","address":"4800 Coplin Street","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"5240","name":"Red Sea Food Inc.","address":"12500 Warren E.","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"1731","name":"Capuchin Kitchen","address":"4390 Conner ","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"839","name":"Hamilton Academy","address":"14223 Southampton Ave.","zipcode":"48213"},{"establishmentid":"5227","name":"Al Namer Fish & Seafood #2 LLC","address":"12332 Warren E.","zipcode":"48215"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"55267","inspectionDate":"2021-07-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the SHELL FISH TAGS","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-07-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"drain lines","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Under the Prep sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Prep cooler","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.12","violationDescription":"Cleaned and SANITIZED EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES  shall be stored only in approved locations.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service and single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored","subProblem":"In toilet room","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"On the floor Single Use Items","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-501.115","violationDescription":"A storage area and enclosure for REFUSE, recyclables, or returnables shall be maintained free of unnecessary items, and clean.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Refuse storage area(s)/enclosures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"At the Rear of the building","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"54518","inspectionDate":"2021-03-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Missing Covered waste container","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room door(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Propped open","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"No Self-serve beverage station","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Missing Wall plugs","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51623404"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}